[
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 1?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 1",
      "os option B 1",
      "os option C 1",
      "os option D 1"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 1",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 2?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 2",
      "os option B 2",
      "os option C 2",
      "os option D 2"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 2",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 3?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 3",
      "os option B 3",
      "os option C 3",
      "os option D 3"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 3",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 3."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 4?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 4",
      "os option B 4",
      "os option C 4",
      "os option D 4"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 4",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 4."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 5?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 5",
      "os option B 5",
      "os option C 5",
      "os option D 5"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 5",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 5."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 6?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 6",
      "os option B 6",
      "os option C 6",
      "os option D 6"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 6",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 6."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 7?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 7",
      "os option B 7",
      "os option C 7",
      "os option D 7"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 7",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 7."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 8?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 8",
      "os option B 8",
      "os option C 8",
      "os option D 8"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 8",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 9?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 9",
      "os option B 9",
      "os option C 9",
      "os option D 9"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 9",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 10?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 10",
      "os option B 10",
      "os option C 10",
      "os option D 10"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 10",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 10."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 11?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 11",
      "os option B 11",
      "os option C 11",
      "os option D 11"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 11",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 11."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 12?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 12",
      "os option B 12",
      "os option C 12",
      "os option D 12"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 12",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 12."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 13?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 13",
      "os option B 13",
      "os option C 13",
      "os option D 13"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 13",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 13."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 14?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 14",
      "os option B 14",
      "os option C 14",
      "os option D 14"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 14",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 14."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 15?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 15",
      "os option B 15",
      "os option C 15",
      "os option D 15"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 15",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 15."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 16?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 16",
      "os option B 16",
      "os option C 16",
      "os option D 16"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 16",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 16."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 17?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 17",
      "os option B 17",
      "os option C 17",
      "os option D 17"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 17",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 17."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 18?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 18",
      "os option B 18",
      "os option C 18",
      "os option D 18"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 18",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 18."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 19?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 19",
      "os option B 19",
      "os option C 19",
      "os option D 19"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 19",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 19."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 20?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 20",
      "os option B 20",
      "os option C 20",
      "os option D 20"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 20",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 20."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 21?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 21",
      "os option B 21",
      "os option C 21",
      "os option D 21"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 21",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 21."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 22?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 22",
      "os option B 22",
      "os option C 22",
      "os option D 22"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 22",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 22."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 23?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 23",
      "os option B 23",
      "os option C 23",
      "os option D 23"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 23",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 23."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 24?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 24",
      "os option B 24",
      "os option C 24",
      "os option D 24"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 24",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 24."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 25?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 25",
      "os option B 25",
      "os option C 25",
      "os option D 25"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 25",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 25."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 26?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 26",
      "os option B 26",
      "os option C 26",
      "os option D 26"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 26",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 26."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 27?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 27",
      "os option B 27",
      "os option C 27",
      "os option D 27"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 27",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 27."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 28?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 28",
      "os option B 28",
      "os option C 28",
      "os option D 28"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 28",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 28."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 29?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 29",
      "os option B 29",
      "os option C 29",
      "os option D 29"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 29",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 29."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 30?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 30",
      "os option B 30",
      "os option C 30",
      "os option D 30"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 30",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 30."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 31?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 31",
      "os option B 31",
      "os option C 31",
      "os option D 31"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 31",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 31."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 32?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 32",
      "os option B 32",
      "os option C 32",
      "os option D 32"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 32",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 32."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 33?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 33",
      "os option B 33",
      "os option C 33",
      "os option D 33"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 33",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 33."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 34?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 34",
      "os option B 34",
      "os option C 34",
      "os option D 34"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 34",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 34."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 35?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 35",
      "os option B 35",
      "os option C 35",
      "os option D 35"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 35",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 35."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 36?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 36",
      "os option B 36",
      "os option C 36",
      "os option D 36"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 36",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 36."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 37?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 37",
      "os option B 37",
      "os option C 37",
      "os option D 37"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 37",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 37."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 38?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 38",
      "os option B 38",
      "os option C 38",
      "os option D 38"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 38",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 38."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 39?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 39",
      "os option B 39",
      "os option C 39",
      "os option D 39"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 39",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 39."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 40?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 40",
      "os option B 40",
      "os option C 40",
      "os option D 40"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 40",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 40."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 41?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 41",
      "os option B 41",
      "os option C 41",
      "os option D 41"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 41",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 41."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 42?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 42",
      "os option B 42",
      "os option C 42",
      "os option D 42"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 42",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 42."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 43?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 43",
      "os option B 43",
      "os option C 43",
      "os option D 43"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 43",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 43."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 44?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 44",
      "os option B 44",
      "os option C 44",
      "os option D 44"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 44",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 44."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 45?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 45",
      "os option B 45",
      "os option C 45",
      "os option D 45"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 45",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 45."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 46?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 46",
      "os option B 46",
      "os option C 46",
      "os option D 46"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 46",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 46."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 47?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 47",
      "os option B 47",
      "os option C 47",
      "os option D 47"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 47",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 47."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 48?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 48",
      "os option B 48",
      "os option C 48",
      "os option D 48"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 48",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 48."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 49?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 49",
      "os option B 49",
      "os option C 49",
      "os option D 49"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 49",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 49."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 50?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 50",
      "os option B 50",
      "os option C 50",
      "os option D 50"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 50",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 50."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 51?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 51",
      "os option B 51",
      "os option C 51",
      "os option D 51"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 51",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 51."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 52?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 52",
      "os option B 52",
      "os option C 52",
      "os option D 52"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 52",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 52."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 53?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 53",
      "os option B 53",
      "os option C 53",
      "os option D 53"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 53",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 53."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 54?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 54",
      "os option B 54",
      "os option C 54",
      "os option D 54"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 54",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 54."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 55?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 55",
      "os option B 55",
      "os option C 55",
      "os option D 55"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 55",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 55."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 56?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 56",
      "os option B 56",
      "os option C 56",
      "os option D 56"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 56",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 56."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 57?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 57",
      "os option B 57",
      "os option C 57",
      "os option D 57"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 57",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 57."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 58?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 58",
      "os option B 58",
      "os option C 58",
      "os option D 58"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 58",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 58."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 59?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 59",
      "os option B 59",
      "os option C 59",
      "os option D 59"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 59",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 59."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 60?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 60",
      "os option B 60",
      "os option C 60",
      "os option D 60"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 60",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 60."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 61?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 61",
      "os option B 61",
      "os option C 61",
      "os option D 61"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 61",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 61."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 62?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 62",
      "os option B 62",
      "os option C 62",
      "os option D 62"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 62",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 62."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 63?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 63",
      "os option B 63",
      "os option C 63",
      "os option D 63"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 63",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 63."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 64?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 64",
      "os option B 64",
      "os option C 64",
      "os option D 64"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 64",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 64."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 65?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 65",
      "os option B 65",
      "os option C 65",
      "os option D 65"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 65",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 65."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 66?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 66",
      "os option B 66",
      "os option C 66",
      "os option D 66"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 66",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 66."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 67?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 67",
      "os option B 67",
      "os option C 67",
      "os option D 67"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 67",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 67."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 68?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 68",
      "os option B 68",
      "os option C 68",
      "os option D 68"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 68",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 68."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 69?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 69",
      "os option B 69",
      "os option C 69",
      "os option D 69"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 69",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 69."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 70?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 70",
      "os option B 70",
      "os option C 70",
      "os option D 70"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 70",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 70."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 71?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 71",
      "os option B 71",
      "os option C 71",
      "os option D 71"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 71",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 71."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 72?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 72",
      "os option B 72",
      "os option C 72",
      "os option D 72"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 72",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 72."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 73?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 73",
      "os option B 73",
      "os option C 73",
      "os option D 73"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 73",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 73."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 74?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 74",
      "os option B 74",
      "os option C 74",
      "os option D 74"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 74",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 74."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 75?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 75",
      "os option B 75",
      "os option C 75",
      "os option D 75"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 75",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 75."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 76?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 76",
      "os option B 76",
      "os option C 76",
      "os option D 76"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 76",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 76."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 77?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 77",
      "os option B 77",
      "os option C 77",
      "os option D 77"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 77",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 77."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 78?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 78",
      "os option B 78",
      "os option C 78",
      "os option D 78"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 78",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 78."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 79?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 79",
      "os option B 79",
      "os option C 79",
      "os option D 79"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 79",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 79."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 80?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 80",
      "os option B 80",
      "os option C 80",
      "os option D 80"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 80",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 80."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 81?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 81",
      "os option B 81",
      "os option C 81",
      "os option D 81"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 81",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 81."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 82?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 82",
      "os option B 82",
      "os option C 82",
      "os option D 82"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 82",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 82."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 83?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 83",
      "os option B 83",
      "os option C 83",
      "os option D 83"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 83",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 83."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 84?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 84",
      "os option B 84",
      "os option C 84",
      "os option D 84"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 84",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 84."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 85?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 85",
      "os option B 85",
      "os option C 85",
      "os option D 85"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 85",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 85."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 86?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 86",
      "os option B 86",
      "os option C 86",
      "os option D 86"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 86",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 86."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 87?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 87",
      "os option B 87",
      "os option C 87",
      "os option D 87"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 87",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 87."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 88?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 88",
      "os option B 88",
      "os option C 88",
      "os option D 88"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 88",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 88."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 89?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 89",
      "os option B 89",
      "os option C 89",
      "os option D 89"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 89",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 89."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 90?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 90",
      "os option B 90",
      "os option C 90",
      "os option D 90"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 90",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 90."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 91?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 91",
      "os option B 91",
      "os option C 91",
      "os option D 91"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 91",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 91."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 92?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 92",
      "os option B 92",
      "os option C 92",
      "os option D 92"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 92",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 92."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 93?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 93",
      "os option B 93",
      "os option C 93",
      "os option D 93"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 93",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 93."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 94?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 94",
      "os option B 94",
      "os option C 94",
      "os option D 94"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 94",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 94."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 95?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 95",
      "os option B 95",
      "os option C 95",
      "os option D 95"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 95",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 95."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 96?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 96",
      "os option B 96",
      "os option C 96",
      "os option D 96"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 96",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 96."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 97?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 97",
      "os option B 97",
      "os option C 97",
      "os option D 97"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 97",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 97."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 98?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 98",
      "os option B 98",
      "os option C 98",
      "os option D 98"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 98",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 98."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 99?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 99",
      "os option B 99",
      "os option C 99",
      "os option D 99"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 99",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 99."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is OS concept 100?",
    "options": [
      "os option A 100",
      "os option B 100",
      "os option C 100",
      "os option D 100"
    ],
    "answer": "os option A 100",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for OS concept 100."
  }
]